Guide to the Tom Law San Francisco Bay Area Punk and Rock Handbill and Poster Collection M1976
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Posters, 3 manuscript boxes, 2 flat boxes and 1 large map folder
  - Folder 9, 1982- 1986 (Box 1)
    12. Gay Video Festival. Every Monday 9:30. Channel 25; San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
    13. Home Delivery; Ansonia Residence Club; 711 Post St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-18; 8.5x11.
    14. Seawolf Proudly Presents Party Entertainment; Seawolf; 706 Oak St. San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 10, 1983- 1986 (Box 1)
    1. Alsino and The Condor; San Francisco Art Institute; 800 Chestnut St. San Francisco, CA; March 28 & 29; 8.5x11.
    2. Show Dogs; 60 6th St. San Francisco, CA; 1983-01-20; 8.5x11.
    3. Freaky Executives; The Fillmore; 1805 Geary Blvd. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-22; 8.5x11.
    4. Human Origins; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; April 22 -- Human Origins; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway San Francisco, CA; April 30 -- Human Origins; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; April 27; 8.5x11.
    5. Flying Color, Mrs. Green; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-04-19; 8.5x11.
    8. Jet Boy, Kix; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; December 6; 8.5x11.
    7. Slantstep; Thom Story; 747 Haight St San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
    8. Frightwig; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-10; 8.5x11.
    9. Godzilla Voice, Alex 5 (music/theater), Jeffrey Kriger (slide show); New Generic; 2 Clinton Park San Francisco, CA; 1984-07; 8.5x11.
    10. Tragic Mulatto, Camper Van Beethoven, The Cat Heads; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-23; 8.5x11.
    11. Mudwomen, Snotgreen Tea, Caroliner Rainbow; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-23; 8.5x11.
    12. My Sin; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-06-14; 8.5x11.
    13. The Naked Into, Pray for Rain; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-28; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 11, 1986- 1986 (Box 1)
    1. Home Of The Brave; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-02; 8.5x11.
    2. Mapenzi; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-05-10; 8.5x11.
    3. Mapenzi; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-14; 8.5x11.
    4. Mapenzi, Joni Haastrup & Friends; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-06-08; 8.5x11.
    5. Meditation, Intergalactic Funkateers; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-08; 8.5x11.
    6. Mess Tent, Salem 66; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-04-29; 8.5x11.
    7. Mapenzi, Unruly World; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; November 8; 8.5x11.
    8. Paranoid Blue, M.J.B., Pleasant Day, 7 Dutch Poets; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA 1986-02-07; 8.5x11.
    9. Party Of Five; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-19; 8.5x11.
    10. Minister Of Control Tony Moses, Jah Big Powerhouse, Capital And Majesty; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11; 8.5x11.
    11. S.O.M., Suffix Adult; California College of Art and Design; San Francisco, CA; 1985-02-23; 8.5x11.
    12. Peace Or Perish Multi-Media Rock Marathon. Benefit For Peace Or Perish - A Crisis Anthology. 50 Rock Bands; Art Exhibit; 59 Performing Poets; Personal Appearance By Miriam Patchen; film; Video Screenings; Light Show; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1983-12; 8.5x11.
    13. Voitek Contemporary & Vintage Clothing; 553 Haight San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 12, 1984- 1986 (Box 1)
    1. Wow!!; California; 8.5x11.
    2. Metro Sensuous; Sound of Music; 162 Turk St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-11 -- Metro Sensuous; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-10 -- Metro Sensuous; DJ Joe; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-08; 8.5x11.
    3. Love Circus, Schrödinger's Cat, Pig Latin, 7 Dutch Poets; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-02; 8.5x11.
    4. Pleasant Day, Caroliner Rainbow, Lennonburger; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-01; 8.5x11.
    5. Pulse; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08; 8.5x11.
    6. Pucci; Lucky Lion; Concord, CA; 1984-11-15 -- Pucci; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-11-02; 8.5x11.
    7. Pulse; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08; 8.5x11.
    8. Haight Ashbury 8th Annual Street Fair; San Francisco, CA; 1985-06-09; 8.5x11.
    9. Pig Latin, The Whitefronts; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-13; 8.5x11.
    10. Pleasant Day, Clown Alley, Calico Basket, Test Subjects; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-25; 8.5x11.
    11. Pleasant Day, Caroliner Rainbow, Lennonburger; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-01; 4.5x5.5.
    12. Pillage People, Sluglords, Swivel, Some II-II, Caroliner Rainbow; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-02-14; 8.5x11.
    13. Memphis G-Spots; Club Nine [Nine]; 399 9th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-25; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 13, 1983- 1986 (Box 1)
    1. Video Circus. An Ambient Light & Video Show; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-07-15; 8.5x11.
    2. Mind Motion Master Mix; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-15; 8.5x11.
    3. Repeat Offenders; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-01-22; 8.5x11.
    4. The Rejected; Frankies "Cool Aid" Featuring Special Guests; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-27; 8.5x11.
    5. The Razers; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-04 -- The Razers; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-22; 8.5x11.
    6. Pucci; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-15 -- Pucci; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway; San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-30; 8.5x11.
    7. Horny Lads (Chip and Tony Kinman Of Rank & File); Club Nine [Nine]; 399 9th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-12; 8.5x11.
    8. Social Unrest, Crucifix, P.L.H., Treason; Valencia Tool & Die; 974 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1983-07-09; 8.5x11.
    9. Shy Hands; 6th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-26; 8.5x11.
    10. Shy Hands; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-22; 8.5x11.
    11. Silent Night, Wages Of Sin, Shiva Dancing; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-25; 8.5x11.
    12. Sea Hags; River Theater; Guerneville, CA; 1985-11-02 -- Sea Hags; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-31 -- Sea Hags; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-01; 8.5x11.
    13. Love Circus, Schrödinger's Cat, Pig Latin, 7 Dutch Poets; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-02; 8.5x11.
    14. Blue Planet [A Film By Franco Piavoli]; Kokusai Theatre; 1700 Post St. San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11 -- No Mondays, Proud Ones, Earwaves; Sound Of Music; 162 Turk St. San Francisco, CA; July 19; 8.5x11 -- Proud Ones, Rock-A-Fellas, Windstorm; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; July 18; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 14, 1984- 1986 (Box 1)
    1. Shadow Image; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-21; 8.5x11.
    2. Shy Hands, Freaky Executives; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-16; 8.5x11.
    3. Shadow Image; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1984_09-29; 8.5x11.
    4. Sea Hags, Jet Boy; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-15; 1986-03-01; 8.5x11.
    5. Shiva Dancing [Siva Dancing], Ku Ku Ku, Celebrity Skin, Pig Latin; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA;1986-03-01; 8.5x11.
    6. Box O' Laffs, The Cat Heads, Slovenly; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-08; 8.5x11.
    7. Sea Hags, Body Nightclub; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; June 18; 8.5x11.
    8. Pleasant Day, 7 Dutch Poets, M.J.B., Paranoid Blue; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-07; 8.5x11.
    9. Shiva Dancing [Siva Dancing], 17 Pygmies, Terra Incognita; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-21; 8.5x11.
    10. Sluglords, Tragic Mulatto, Short Dogs Grow, Noize Boyz; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-16; 8.5x11.
    11. Yo, Slovenly, The Cat Heads; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-26; 8.5x11.
    12. Tomorrow's Children; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
    13. Too Much Fun; 702 15th St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-10-26; 8.5x11.
    14. Too Much Fun; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 15, 1985- 1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    1. The Stupeds; Baybrick Inn; 1190 Folsom St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-07; 8.5x11.
    2. Temper Temper; Liquid Sky; 3316 24th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-20; 8.5x11.
    3. Social Unrest, Carrion Commandoes, Stick Against Stone, Crash n' Burn, Brain Rust, M.J.B., Tito [Rock Against AIDS, Rock For Life]; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-15; 8.5x11.
    4. Strappado; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-06; 8.5x11.
    5. After Hours. New Dance, New Video, New Stone. The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; Fridays & Saturdays; 8.5x11.
    6. Spot 1019, Burning Rain, The Thongs; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-19; 8.5x11.
    7. Special Fun; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-17; 8.5x11.
    8. Sound Policy; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-06-07; 8.5x11.
    9. Specimen; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francsico, CA; November 2; 8.5x11.
    10. The Stickers, Whorl, Boss Hoss; Sound of Music; 162 Turk St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-22; 8.5x11.
    11. Stick Figures; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-02-21; 8.5x11.
    12. The Strand; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-11; 8.5x11.
    13. Stick Figures; Uncle Charlie's; Corte Madera, CA; 1985-01-23 -- Stick Figures; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-01-16; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 16, 1984- 1986 (Box 1)
    1. Spot 1019, Zero; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-13; 8.5x11.
    2. Speed Queens, Smashed Weekend; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-04-15; 8.5x11.
    3. Stick Against Stone; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francsico, CA; 1985-09-08; 8.5x11.
    4. Silent Night; Berkeley Square; 1333 University Ave. Berkeley, CA; 1986-01-07 -- Silent Night, Wages Of Sin, Legal Reins; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-10; 8.5x11.
    5. Tragic Mulatto, The Babel Trees, The Hot Combs; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-17; 8.5x11.
    6. Too Much Fun, African Soundz, Unruly World; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-17; 3x5.
    7. Switching Yard, Mrs. Green, Domino Theory; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; August 28; 8.5x11.
    8. Ten Tall Men, The Grifters; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-30; 8.5x11.
    9. Terminal Man; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-17; 8.5x11.
    10. Toxic Reasons, M.I.A., Whipping Boy, Special Forces; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-03-01; 8.5x11.
    11. Trial, The Invertebrates, The Muskrats; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-07-28; 8.5x11.
    12. Candlelight March For Harvey Milk And George Moscone; San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-27; 8.5x11 -- Translator, Mrs. Green, Blue Movie; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; November 30; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 17, 1984- 1986 (Box 1)
    1. Our Lady Of Pain; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-24; 8.5x11.
    2. Paranoid Blue, Pleasant Day, Schrödinger's Cat, Heru-Ra-Ha; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-12; 8.5x11.
    3. The Afflicted, Blood, Sweat & Steel Toes, Cardnil Sin, Losing It; Adina; 1684 Hudson Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-28; 8.5x11.
    4. X-Tal; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; January 10; 8.5x11.
    5. The Dave, Mark Eitzel + Ruby, Ultimately Sammy Nome, Scott Alexander, Steve Clark, Gulf Of The Faralones, Beth Custer, Invertebrates, Brent Hoover, Mantra + Mike, Davenports; Sound Of Music; 162 Turk St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-31; 8.5x11.
    6. Until December; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-23; 8.5x11.
    7. Tripod Jimmie, Mess Tent, Typhoon; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-20; 8.5x11.
    8. Typhoon; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; August 21; 8.5x11.
    9. Typhoon; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; November 21; 8.5x11.
    10. 23 Screams, The New Pukes, Sacra-Political; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; May 31; 8.5x11.
    11. The Nuns, Bar Wars Ballet, Third Wave Dance Theatre, Cecelia-Marie Bowman, Cece Chevere, Blanche Brown, Dancers Working, Ava & Andre, Ken Blakey, Ron Peterson; Palace of Fine Arts Theatre; 3301 Lyon St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-06; 8.5x11 -- Ugly Americans, Front, The (San Diego), Spot 1019, Victim's Family, Christ On Parade; New Method Warehouse; 3623 Adeline St. Emeryville, CA; 1985-12-22; 8.5x11.
    12. Translator; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-12; 8.5x11.
    13. Neighbors; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-07-21; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 18, 1984- 1986 (Box 1)
    1. Nimbus, Glorious Din, Shiva Dancing; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-11; 8.5x11.
    2. Noize Boyz; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA -- Noize Boyz; Hotel Utah; 584 4th St. San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
    3. No Mondays, Plateau, Rox; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-06-20; 8.5x11.
    4. Noumenon; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-06-28; 8.5x11.
    5. Naomi Vice with Naomi Eisenberg; Wolfgang's; 901 Columbus Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-18; 8.5x11.
    6. The Offenders, The Dicks, Condemned To Death; Valencia Tool & Die; 974 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-01-15; 8.5x11.
    7. Gary Floyd; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-07; 8.5x11.
    8. Necropolis Of Love, Dj Bernard; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-05-04; 8.5x11.
    9. Neurotic Distortion; The Lab; 1805 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; December 14, 15; 8.5x11.
    10. The Nice Boys From New York, Parri Troy; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-29 -- Jimmy Pugh Thang; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-30; 8.5x11.
    11. Nighteye, Last Rites, Misled, The Softies; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-01-24; 8.5x11.
    12. Parade; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-08; 8.5x11.
    13. Necropolis Of Love; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-18; 8.5x11.
    14. The Muskrats, Boo!; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-27; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 19, 1984- 1986 (Box 1)
    1. Mudwomen, Snotgreen Tea, Caroliner Rainbow; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-23; 8.5x11.
    2. My Sin, The Maids, 7 Dutch Poets; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-18; 8.5x11.
    3. The Naked Into; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-03; 8.5x11.
    4. The Nashville Ramblers (from San Diego), The Deadbeats, The Bohemians, The Social Eye; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-15; 8.5x11.
    5. My Sin, Shadow Image; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-11-24; 8.5x11.
    6. Mudwomen, Snotgreen Tea, Caroliner Rainbow; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-23; 8.5x11. [World Premiere Of The Fabulous Mudwomen].
    7. Morticia, Pleasant Day, Ricky Williams, The Ophelias, Love Circus, 3 Mouse Guitars, Bwana Devils, The Cat Heads; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-05; 8.5x11.
    8. Mrs. Green; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; August 28; 8.5x11.
    9. The Murmurs; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; March 16; 8.5x11.
    10. Morally Bankrupt, Bad Habit, Jackal, Armageddon Light Company, Films By Steve Mann & J.R. Swanson; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-28; 8.5x11.
    11. Morally Bankrupt, Burning Witches, Crash n' Burn, Typhoon; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-05-17; 8.5x11.
    12. The Mud Dogs; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; June 30; 8.5x11.
    13. The Morlocks, Sea Hags, The Whitefronts; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-15; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 20, 1984- 1986 (Box 1)
    1. Mrs. Green; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-06?; 8.5x11.
    2. Mrs. Green, Blue Movie; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; September 18; 8.5x11.
    3. Mess Tent, The Zarcons, Nonfiction; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; January 16; 8.5x11.
    4. The Monikers; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-28; 8.5x11.
    5. The Monikers; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-12; 8.5x11.
    6. Michael Rose; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-04; 8.5x11.
    7. Michael Rose; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-05; 8.5x11.
    8. Mindbreakers; Sound of Music; 162 Turk St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-24; 8.5x11.
    9. Mess Tent, The Witnesses; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-30; 8.5x11.
    10. The Mud Dogs; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-07; 8.5x11.
    11. Open Dance Auditions For Dance Floor 86, The Bay Area's Premier TV Dance Show; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-10; 8.5x11.
    12. Mess Tent, The Afflicted, The Witnesses; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; March 30; 8.5x11.
    13. SF Gay Video Festival. Every Monday Nite 9:30. Cable 25; San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
    14. Dream Sequence. A Group Show; Beef Gallery; 659 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; December 19th [reception]; 8.5x11.
    15. Gaslight; San Francisco, CA; June 15 & 16, 80 [?]; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 21, 1982- 1986 (Box 1, Box 21)
    1. Social Fabric; Heaven's Gate; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1982-10-21 -- Social Fabric; Hotel Utah; 584 4th St. San Francisco, CA; 1982-10-23; 8.5x11.
    2. Doris Fish, Phillip R. Ford; [Club 181]; 181 Eddy St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12; 8.5x11.
    3. Third Wave Dance. Full Moon Dream. Dancing, Video, Lights. New Dance Music; Liquid Sky; 3316 24th St. San Francisco, CA; January 25; 8.5x11.
    4. Your Tenderloin Rock Shop [etc.]; The Corner On Market; 1100 Market St. San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
    5. [photo of couples dancing to Jerry Lee Lewis, with a dotted line arrow]; 8.5x11.
    6. Minoy, EX.I 23, Number 5, Secret Chiefs; Artists' Television Access (ATA); 220 8th St. San Francisco, CA; January 25; 8.5x11.
    7. Nelson & Winnie Mandela, Woza Albert; Media [Mad Movies At Media]; 360 9th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-26 -- Media [Mad Movies At Media]; 360 9th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-03; 8.5x11.
    8. Quarantine; San Francisco, CA; 1985-04-29; 8.5x11.
    9. Ruin; San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
    10. On The 40th Anniversary of Hiroshima, Say Hi to The Bomb Makers; University of California, Berkeley. University Hall; Berkeley, CA; 1985-08-05 -- 40th Anniversary of Hiroshima/Nagasaki; Golden Gate Bridge; San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-06; 8.5x11.
    11. Vintage Clothing Plus Accessories. Grand Opening; Carnivorous; 629 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 8.5x11.
    12. Beef Gallery [Beef Art Collective]; 659 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-05; 8.5x11.
    13. Missing. Michael David Chaves. If Seen, Have Him Call Home. We Still Love You Mike; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 22, 1984- 1986 (Box 1)
    1. Fallen Angel; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-30; 8.5x11.
    2. Altar De Fey; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-17; 8.5x11.
    3. Flying Color; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-15 -- Jain; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-16; 8.5x11.
    4. Fade To Black, Our Lady Of Pain, Nothing Sacred; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-08-31; 8.5x11.
    5. Black Athletes, DJ Veronika; 16th Note/Firehouse 7; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; Fri. 18; 8.5x11.
    6. Just Hipp; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway San Francisco, CA; November 11; 8.5x11.
    7. Reagan's 'Brothers" In Action--No Brother Of Mine. No Aid To The Contra; 1984; 8.5x11.
    8. Jet Boy; Ruthie's Inn; 2618 San Pablo Ave. Berkeley, CA; 1986-04-19; 8.5x11.
    9. Michigan & Smiley with Legal Aliens, Rankin' Scroo & Ginger with Ridim Section; Wolfgang's; 901 Columbus Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-02; 8.5x11.
    10. Ku Ku Ku, Bob Carroll & "The Dirt Show"; Noe Valley Ministry; 1021 Sanchez St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-08; 8.5x11.
    11. Ku Ku Ku, DJ Calamity, Dot 3; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-06-27; 8.5x11.
    12. Kelly Brock's Romans, The Detectors, Yo, Mindz Eye; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-10-18; 8.5x11.
    13. Jon Gon; Industrial Dance Company; 2140 Market St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-26; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 23, 1983- 1986 (Box 1)
    1. Lethal Gospel; [Plus A Video from Dirk Dirksen: Dead Kennedys Last Night On Broadway]; San Francisco State. Student Union, Barbary Coast; 1650 Holloway Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-01; 8.5x11.
    2. Leon Russell; San Francisco State. Student Union. Barbary Coast; 1650 Holloway Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1983-12-06; 8.5x11.
    3. Leroy Smart, Raskidus; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-30; 8.5x11.
    4. Lethal Gospel; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-28; 8.5x11.
    5. Les Nickelettes. Anarchy In High Heels; Club 181; 181 Eddy St. San Francisco, CA; March 4-5; 8.5x11.
    6. Home Of The Brave; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-27 -- Home Of The Brave; The New Ice Age; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-01; 8.5x11.
    7. Elliot Schneider and The Banned, Wages Of Sin, Ku Ku Ku; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-15; 8.5x11.
    8. Cult Of Bigness; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-06-05; 8.5x11.
    9. The Cat Heads, Spot 1019; 16th Note / Firehouse 7; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; April 17; 8.5x11.
    10. Orchestral Manoeuvres In The Dark, Group 87, My Sin; Kabuki Nightclub; 1881 Post St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-07-30; 8.5x11.
    11. Savage Republic, Black Athletes, Slovenly; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-25 -- The Alleycats AKA The Zarkons, Screamin' Sirens, Sea Hags, House Of Wheels; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-22; 8.5x11.
    12. Sea Hags, The Alleycats, Screamin' Sirens, House Of Wheels; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-22; 8.5x11.
    13. The Scropes; Sound of Music; 162 Turk St. San Francisco, CA; 1983-04-06; 8.5x11.
  - Folder 24, 1983- 1986 (Box 1)
    1. Chuck Z. Incubus Performance + Video Tapes; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; April 24; 8.5x11.
    2. Voluntary Living; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-08; 8.5x11.
    3. Jungle Dinner; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; September 26; 8.5x11.
    4. Code Of The West; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; April 11 -- Code Of The West; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; April 16; 8.5x11.
    5. 84 Rooms, Whiskey Worms; Hotel Utah; 584 4th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-03; 8.5x11.
    6. Frontline Rockers; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-15; 8.5x11.
    7. Party Of Five; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-05-31; 8.5x11.
    8. Early Man, Plastic Medium; The Stud; 1535 Folsom St. San Francisco, CA; 1983-04-10; 8.5x11.